[
  {
    "question": "ア",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "e",
      "a",
      "u",
      "i"
    ],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "i",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "エ",
      "ア",
      "イ",
      "ウ"
    ],
    "answer": "イ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ウ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "i",
      "u",
      "o",
      "a"
    ],
    "answer": "u"
  },
  {
    "question": "e",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "オ",
      "エ",
      "ア",
      "ウ"
    ],
    "answer": "エ"
  },
  {
    "question": "オ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "u",
      "o",
      "a",
      "e"
    ],
    "answer": "o"
  },
  {
    "question": "ka",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "コ",
      "カ",
      "ク",
      "キ"
    ],
    "answer": "カ"
  },
  {
    "question": "キ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ki",
      "ku",
      "ka",
      "ke"
    ],
    "answer": "ki"
  },
  {
    "question": "ku",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "カ",
      "ク",
      "キ",
      "コ"
    ],
    "answer": "ク"
  },
  {
    "question": "ケ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ki",
      "ke",
      "ko",
      "ka"
    ],
    "answer": "ke"
  },
  {
    "question": "ko",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ケ",
      "ク",
      "コ",
      "カ"
    ],
    "answer": "コ"
  },
  {
    "question": "サ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "se",
      "so",
      "sa",
      "shi"
    ],
    "answer": "sa"
  },
  {
    "question": "shi",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ス",
      "シ",
      "サ",
      "キ"
    ],
    "answer": "シ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ス",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "so",
      "se",
      "su",
      "tsu"
    ],
    "answer": "su"
  },
  {
    "question": "se",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "サ",
      "セ",
      "ソ",
      "シ"
    ],
    "answer": "セ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ソ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "su",
      "se",
      "so",
      "sa"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "ta",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "テ",
      "タ",
      "だ",
      "ト"
    ],
    "answer": "タ"
  },
  {
    "question": "チ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "shi",
      "tsu",
      "chi",
      "cha"
    ],
    "answer": "chi"
  },
  {
    "question": "tsu",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "チ",
      "ツ",
      "ス",
      "ず"
    ],
    "answer": "ツ"
  },
  {
    "question": "テ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ne",
      "to",
      "te",
      "ta"
    ],
    "answer": "te"
  },
  {
    "question": "to",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "タ",
      "ト",
      "テ",
      "ど"
    ],
    "answer": "ト"
  },
  {
    "question": "ナ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "nu",
      "ne",
      "na",
      "ni"
    ],
    "answer": "na"
  },
  {
    "question": "ni",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ヌ",
      "ネ",
      "ニ",
      "ナ"
    ],
    "answer": "ニ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ヌ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "mu",
      "nu",
      "ni",
      "no"
    ],
    "answer": "nu"
  },
  {
    "question": "ne",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ナ",
      "ネ",
      "ヌ",
      "レ"
    ],
    "answer": "ネ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ノ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "nu",
      "no",
      "na",
      "to"
    ],
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "ha",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ワ",
      "ば",
      "ハ",
      "ホ"
    ],
    "answer": "ハ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ヒ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "fu",
      "bi",
      "hi",
      "ki"
    ],
    "answer": "hi"
  },
  {
    "question": "fu",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ぷ",
      "フ",
      "ぶ",
      "ハ"
    ],
    "answer": "フ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ヘ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ha",
      "he",
      "e",
      "ne"
    ],
    "answer": "he"
  },
  {
    "question": "ho",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ヘ",
      "ホ",
      "ヲ",
      "ハ"
    ],
    "answer": "ホ"
  },
  {
    "question": "マ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "mu",
      "ma",
      "mo",
      "na"
    ],
    "answer": "ma"
  },
  {
    "question": "mi",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "マ",
      "ニ",
      "ミ",
      "ム"
    ],
    "answer": "ミ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ム",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "me",
      "mu",
      "nu",
      "ma"
    ],
    "answer": "mu"
  },
  {
    "question": "me",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ム",
      "メ",
      "マ",
      "ネ"
    ],
    "answer": "メ"
  },
  {
    "question": "モ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ma",
      "mu",
      "mo",
      "no"
    ],
    "answer": "mo"
  },
  {
    "question": "ya",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ワ",
      "ユ",
      "ヤ",
      "ヨ"
    ],
    "answer": "ヤ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ユ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ya",
      "yu",
      "yo",
      "ru"
    ],
    "answer": "yu"
  },
  {
    "question": "yo",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ロ",
      "ヨ",
      "ユ",
      "ヤ"
    ],
    "answer": "ヨ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ラ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ri",
      "ra",
      "na",
      "la"
    ],
    "answer": "ra"
  },
  {
    "question": "ri",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "レ",
      "ラ",
      "リ",
      "ル"
    ],
    "answer": "リ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ル",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ro",
      "ri",
      "ra",
      "ru"
    ],
    "answer": "ru"
  },
  {
    "question": "re",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ル",
      "レ",
      "ラ",
      "リ"
    ],
    "answer": "レ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ロ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "ru",
      "ro",
      "ra",
      "re"
    ],
    "answer": "ro"
  },
  {
    "question": "wa",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ヲ",
      "ラ",
      "ワ",
      "が"
    ],
    "answer": "ワ"
  },
  {
    "question": "ヲ",
    "type": "kana-to-romaji",
    "options": [
      "o",
      "wo",
      "wa",
      "mo"
    ],
    "answer": "wo"
  },
  {
    "question": "n",
    "type": "romaji-to-kana",
    "options": [
      "ヌ",
      "ン",
      "ム",
      "ラ"
    ],
    "answer": "ン"
  }
]
